6ave.com 2011-11-30

# 6ave.com

**Purchases**  
6ave.com allows our customers to purchase products online. In order to process these orders, we must collect your full name, billing address, shipping address, telephone numbers, email address, and credit card information including the type of card, the card number, the expiration date, and the card holder's name. This information is collected and transmitted using secure technology provided by VeriSign, Inc. and Hacker Safe. It is stored by us on our secure servers to allow us to perform essential functions including processing credit card reconciliations, providing customer service, and handling audits and warranty claims.

As a convenience to our online purchasers, we offer the option of storing your personal information (but not credit card information) in a customer account. This makes shopping easier for our repeat customers, as they will not have to reenter their information every time they make a purchase. Users who choose this option will enter their email address and select a password, which will be the only way this information can be accessed. They will be able to change this information at any time. Customers who want to delete access to their online profiles can do so by contacting 

Customer Service

**Mailing List**  
We also allow our users to sign up to receive Savings & News by registering with their email addresses, or by checking the appropriate box when purchasing. Users can remove their information from our mailing list at any time by sending an email with those instructions to [unsubscribe@6ave.com](mailto:unsubscribe@6ave.com). In addition, every email from us will come with instructions explaining how to unsubscribe. 

**Sharing Information**  
6ave.com respects your right to privacy. Protecting this right is something we take very seriously.  As a result, we do not share your information with any non-sanctioned third party. When necessary, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html)

**Security**  
6ave.com is dedicated to providing our online customers with a safe and secure shopping experience. We use the latest encryption technology to protect your personal information. In addition, we use secure socket layer (SSL) technology with digital certificates by VeriSign, Inc. and Hacker Safe.  All of your personal information is stored on our password protected secure servers.

**Cookies/Other Data Collection**  
A cookie is information that is stored by the server on the client side of a client/server communication. Typically, a cookie records your preferences when using a particular site. They can also be used to customize pages for you based on your browser type or other information you may have provided the website. Web users must agree to let cookies be saved for them, however keep in mind that in most cases they help to provide you with a better shopping experience.  Cookies may be used to enable us to keep track of your shopping cart and recently viewed items, and to otherwise customize your shopping experience. As we respect your privacy, you may set your browser to refuse the cookies automatically or you can manually erase them from your browser. 

For our internal purposes, we gather date, time, pages visited, originating search engine, and IP address of all visitors to our site. We keep this information for our internal security audit log and systems administration purposes, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We also use this information to better serve you, as it enable us to provide a shopping experience that is customized to your interests and product needs

.

**** California Privacy Rights

Residents of California have the right to obtain certain information from a business with which they have established a relationship.  California residents are entitled to information identifying all companies with which their personal information has been shared within the past year, as well as any personal information used for that company’s direct marketing purposes. They are also entitled to a description of the categories of personal information that has been disclosed. **6ave.com does not share our customers’ personal information with any third party** **.**

**Children's Online Privacy**

Sixth Avenue Electronics is committed to protecting the privacy of children.  In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, 6ave.com does not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13, nor do we sell products directly to children under 13.  If you are a child under the age of 13, you must ask a parent or guardian to assist you when visiting our site.

**Links To Other Sites**  
6ave.com may link to other sites. We are not responsible for the content of these sites or how they may use your information.  We advise you to look at their privacy policies and contact them directly with any questions. 

**Accessing and Editing Personal Information**

When you sign up for an account at 6ave.com, you may store your personal information, but not your credit card information, to make checkout more convenient in the future. You may access or change this information at any time by logging into your account. Setting up an account is optional, and you may make a purchase without doing so.  In this case, your personal information will not be stored and you must reenter it when making purchases in the future.

** Changes to Our Policy**

We reserve the right to make changes to our privacy policy at any time and without prior notice.  If any significant changes are made, our customers will be notified. To continue using our site after such changes are made signifies your consent to these changes.
